本字幕由大家字幕组原创翻译制作，仅供学习，禁止用于任何商业盈利行为。若因私自散布传播造成法律问题，本字幕组概不负责。更多影视请搜索并关注新浪微博@大家字幕组。
很好 做得不错
All right, I like this.
当我说云 你们说九 云
When I say cloud, you say nine. Cloud.
- 九 - 云
- Nine. - Cloud.
- 九 - 我说团队 你说合作
- Nine. - When I say team, you say work.
EVERYONE
- 团队! - 合作 - 团队! - 合作
- Team! - Work. - Team! - Work.
关注新浪微博
@大家字幕组
- 我们是云一吗? - 不是!
- Are we cloud one? - No!
- 我们是云二吗? - 不是!
- Are we cloud two? - No!
- 我们是云三吗? - 不是!
- Are we cloud three? - No!
微 信 关 注
dajiazimuzu
我们是云...
Are we cloud...
这动员会的词好像有点长啊
This chant seems a little on the long side.
一年比一年长
Gets longer every year.
我刚来的时候 我们只要围成一圈
When I first started here, we would just
伸个手 说句"耶"就行了
put our hands in the middle and go, "Yay."
不是!
No!
我们是云九吗?
Are we Cloud 9?
是的!
Yeah!
没错!
没错! 顾客永远是对的
Yeah! The customer's always right.
没错!
Oh, yeah!
- 他们不会错 - 没错!
- They are not wrong. - Oh, yeah!
- 这就是为什么 - 啊哈!
- And that is why. - Oh, yeah!
- 我们唱这首歌 - 明白!
- We sing this song. Oh, yeah!
我们是!
We are!
云九
Cloud 9.
我们是云九
We are Cloud 9.
8 7 6 5
Eight, seven, six, five,
4 3 2 1!
four, three, two, one!
起飞!
Blast off!
给我个"C"!
Now give me a "C"!
C!
超级商店
第一季 第三集
大家字幕组 欢乐出品
在我们开门之前 我需要一个志愿者
Before we open, I need a volunteer
翻译    树树   Davion
给顾客发放
to hand out samples of the new
翻译    树树   Davion
最新云九牌萨尔萨辣酱
Cloud 9 brand salsa, senior cloud.
翻译     累   鑫鑫美少女
这里 我来吧
Yes, right here. I'll do it.
校对     My Life
很好 但我并不是因为
Yes, perfect, and I don't mean
校对     My Life
你是墨西哥人才选的你哦
just because you're Mexican.
时间轴     六级求过的风   Papersun
我是菲律宾人
I'm actually Pilipino.
时间轴     六级求过的风   Papersun
好吧 那我给其他人一个机会
Okay, let's consider all our options.
特效     福娃
艾米 我有预感这事交给你最合适
Um, Amy, I've got a feeling this is right up your alley.
特效     福娃
压制     冰岛
就因为我是拉丁裔的?
Because I'm Latina?
不不 这和种族一点关系都没有
No, it has nothing to do with race.
你只是天生给人一种火辣的感觉
You just have a certain natural spiciness.
不要
No.
好吧 那算了
Okay, you know, fine, I'll just, uh,
我就随机选一个人
pick someone at random.
挑兵挑将
Eeny, Meeny, Miney, Mo.
骑马打仗
Jesus saved us long ago.
谁是我的
Don't believe me, what a shame.
好兵好将
Judgment day you'll be in flames.
- 另一个拉丁裔? - 啥玩意?
- The other Latina? - What?
我来吧
I could do it.
那场面肯定笑尿了
That'd be hilarious.
你会被打扮成斗牛士
You should dress like a matador.
其实 我没意见
Honestly, it's fine.
这比打扫更衣室要好多了
It beats a day of dressing room duty.
谢谢 怎么打扮你 快想一下
Thank you. Think fast!
墨西哥帽!
Mexico hat!
云九顾客请注意
Attention, Cloud 9 shoppers,
请去食品区品尝
Be sure to stop by grocery
免费萨尔萨辣酱
for a free sample of senior cloud salsa.
药品区现在可以打预防针
And in pharmacy, get yourself a flu shot,
有中等 清淡 哎呀呀不同品种
available in medium, mild, ay-yi-yi picante,
我敢肯定这是别人写错了
And I'm almost positive that was written down wrong.
没错 萨尔萨辣酱
yes, senior cloud salsa
特别适合聚会食用
is very good for parties.
口味繁多
And there are so many flavors.
她是堪萨斯的
She is from Kansas City.
为啥说话像飞毛腿冈萨雷斯(西班牙卡通形象)?
Why is she talking like speedy Gonzales?
我应该和她谈谈
I should say something to her.
千万别
Absolutely not.
别狗拿耗子多管闲事
Do not get involved in things that don't concern you.
人都和流沙一样 会把你吸进去
People here are quicksand. They will suck you in.
你的意思是不要帮助任何人?
So you're saying never help anyone?
我是说别帮这家店里的人
I'm saying don't help anyone in this store.
在这四面墙之间 帮助别人就如身处流沙之中
Within these walls, helping is quicksand.
你知道吗 我特别开心你提到"墙"这个字
You know, it's funny that you mention walls.
因为有年夏天我参加人道主义援助
Because that summer that I spent doing habitat for humanity,
我真的建造了...
I was literally building...
- 怎么了 - 你吧
- What? - You know,
总是不断地提起这事
You find ways to work that into conversation a lot.
我和你聊天时
I try not to say words like "Hammer"
已经尽量不去提"锤子"和"房顶"了
or "Roof" When I'm around you.
有次我们聊休·劳瑞 你都能扯到这个
One time you got there from Hugh Laurie.
我的意思是 有些人是毒瘤 消极怠工
Look, my point is, there are people who do nothing
有些人是真抓实干的
and there are people who do something,
我就是那部分人
And I am one of those people.
真正... 干活的那部分
The... the something group.
失陪了
Excuse me.
先生 有什么需要帮忙的吗?
Sir, is there something I can help you with?
真的吗? 太好了
Really? Uh, wow, yes,
非常感谢
uh, thank you so much.
太棒了
Oh, that's great.
把这些盒子堆到药房去
So, uh, just stack 'em in the pharmacy,
后面卡车里还有不少
and then there's gonna be a few more loads in the trucks.
- 后面还有? - 还有很多呢
- Oh, there's more? - Oh, so many more.
既然这样 那我去喝杯咖啡
Okay. Guess I'm gonna grab a coffee.
萨尔萨辣酱非尝不可
Have to have the salsa.
有时我喜欢抹些粘果酸浆
Sometimes I like the tomatillo
在油炸玉米粉饼上 但也不是一直这样
with the quesadilla, but not all the time.
- 我要和她谈谈 - 别啊
- I'm gonna say something. - Don't do it.
帮我讲解一下
Now, just walk me through some of the features
不同牙刷的效用吧
on some of these guys.
因为很多牙刷都写着能抑制噬菌斑
Cause a lot of 'em are saying they do plaque control.
我主要是想驱除牙垢
My concern, specifically, is tartar.
好的 额...
Okay, well, um...
我长了很多牙垢
I'm a bit of a tartar guy.
我的口腔保健师和我说
Yeah, my hygienist told me
她从没见过我这样牙垢这么多的人
she'd never seen someone with so much tartar.
我还以为那是好东西呢
I thought that was a good thing.
其实并不是啊
Um, it's not.
来领流感疫苗吧
你知道吗 我俩是一类人
You know, you and me, we're the same.
都是高成就的人
Mm-hmm. Overachievers.
- 没错 - 是吧 我很强硬吗?
- Yeah. - Yeah, am I tough?
算是吧 但我是个药剂师
Uh, yeah, but I'm a pharmacist.
我必须强硬 不然人们就没救了
I have to be tough, or people die.
他们不是付钱来让我偷懒的
They don't pay me what they pay me to slack off.
我年薪有116,670美元
It's $116,670 a year.
所以我觉得自己还挺给力的
Yeah, so I'm doing pretty well for myself.
好吧 如果你要帮忙
Well, listen, uh, if you need anything else
你知道去哪找我
you know where to find me.
好极了 那就去拿点儿酒精湿巾和绷带过来
Great, so grab some alcohol wipes, bandages,
还有无菌纱布垫
and sterile gauze pads.
把第一个病人带进来 给他准备好
Bring in the first patient and prep him.
小伙儿 我们可有很多事要做呢
Man, we got a long day ahead of us.
药房
来领流感疫苗吧
嘿 你知道格伦是不能
Hey, you know Glenn's not allowed
要求你用这种口音说话的对吧?
to ask you to put on that accent, right?
我的意思是 我知道他是经理
I mean, I know he's the manager,
但这也就是能让他随时
But it just means he can use the bathroom
去上厕所而已
without asking anyone.
我知道啊 是我自己想用这个口音
No, I know that. I decided on the accent.
天哪 人们爱死了
Oh my god, people love it.
你好啊 女士
Hola, señorita,
你想把今天过成一个节日吗?
You want to make your day a fiesta?
当然 谢谢你
Sure. Thank you.
- 看见了吧? - 是啊 有些人爱死了
- See? - Yep, some people love it,
但是呢 有些人可能会觉得有点受到冒犯
And, uh, and some people might find it offensive.
冒犯? 你说谁?
Offensive? Like, who?
哦 我不知道
Oh, I don't know...
也许拉丁裔的人会任务
Maybe latino people who would think that
你在利用你们民族的遗产
you're exploiting your heritage
还贬低了你自己
and demeaning yourself.
好吧 随你
Okay, all right,
我不知道你怎么就成了拉丁裔警察了
I don't know who made you latino police,
- 艾米 但是我只是想卖掉这些辣酱 - 不 我不是在
- Amy, but I'm just trying to sell salsa.- No, I am not
- 多管你的闲事 - 好吧 如果你要一直...
- policing you. - Okay, if you could keep...
我只是建议你也许你没有必要...
I'm merely suggesting that maybe you don't need to resort...
你好 女士 您好吗?
Hola, señorita! Como estas?
哦 这是墨西哥番茄酱吗?
Ooh, is that mexican ketchup?
是啊 介个糙好此
"Jess, es berry" Good.
你是说 "是的 这个超好吃"
You mean, "Yes, it's very good."
哦 别听她的
Oh, don't listen to her.
你英语说得棒极了
You speak the language beautifully.
谢谢您 女士
Gracias, señorita.
你想来点儿特别的东西吗?
You want to try something special?
这是你们所说的 菠萝
This is, cómo se dice, pineapple.
好了 你猜怎么着? 够了
Okay, you know what? Stop.
不 你才够了
No! You stop.
像正常人一样说话
Talk like a normal person!
抱歉 小姐 但是她就是在正常说话啊
Excuse me, miss, but she is a normal person.
可不是嘛
That's exactly what I'm saying!
哦 他妈的
Ow! Damn it!
我去你妈 艾米
Mother, Amy! , aye!
搞什么鬼!
What the !
瞧见了? 假的口音
See? Fake accent.
这就是你长了个脆弱的脚踝骨的后果
This is what you get when you've got weak joints.
这就是我为什么在健身房苦练我的脚踝
That's why I have a dedicated ankle day at the gym.
我真的很抱歉 卡门
I really am sorry, Carmen.
我觉得很糟糕
I-I-I feel awful.
是啊 你活该 艾米 本来根本不关你的事
Yeah, you should, Amy. It was none of your business.
好吧 说明一下
Well, just to clarify,
我很抱歉你受伤了
Uh, I feel awful you hurt yourself.
但我还是保持原来的立场
I still stand by my comments.
好了 来吧
Okay, there you go.
哦 想喝水你就拿一瓶吧
Oh, and feel free to take a water.
我不上班的时候是个优步司机
I'm an uber driver in my spare time.
我会把你的东西放在橱子里的
I'll put your stuff in your locker for you.
而且我已经帮你考好勤了
And I already clocked out for you,
所以你不在的时候
so you're not gonna get paid
不会拿到一份工钱的
for any of the time you missed.
别担心
Don't you worry about that.
你真的觉得我不能开车送她吗?
Are you sure I can't drive her?
不用了 我本来就打算今天去趟医院
No, I've been meaning to drop by the hospital anyway.
我喜欢一直盯着那些新生婴儿
I like staring at the newborn babies
直到被别人哄走
until someone asks me to leave.
哦 但是我确实需要有人
Oh, but I do need someone
去接手那个墨西哥酱摊子
to take over the senior cloud salsa stand.
好吧 我会找其他人的
Fine, I'll get somebody else.
但这真的太遗憾了  因为那顶帽子真的
But it's a real shame, because that sombrero
在深一点的肤色上更好看
really pops on darker skin.
好了 那么你有任何关于
Okay, so do you have any questions
氢氯噻嗪的问题吗?
about the hydrochlorothiazide?
没有 你能帮我把这些别的东西
No, uh, could you also ring up
都结一下帐吗?
a few other things for me, please?
当然 好的
Sure, yeah.
我有一个药学博士学位
I have a doctorate in pharmacy,
所以这真的一点都不浪费时间
so this is a great use of my time.
- 我生来就是为了服务大众 - 谢谢你
- I live to serve. - Thank you.
伯妮丝 他同意了
Bernice, he said it's fine.
我的天啊
Oh, god.
等一下
One moment.
嘿 伙计 我需要
Hey, j-dog, I have to, uh,
去舒展一下筋骨
go do some tranquility lunges,
所以你能替我给那家伙打一针吗?
so could you give that guy his shot for me?
哦 不 我不行 我不是个药剂师
Oh, no, I can't. I'm not a pharmacist.
是啊 我还不是一个营业员呢
Yeah, and I'm not a clerk,
但我猜当今世界就是这么迷幻 对吧?
But I guess the world's all topsy-turvy today, isn't it?
动动脑子
Just think!
我只是想找个日常用的牙刷
I'm just basically looking for an every day brush.
就是那种 马毛的
Yeah, just kind of that workhorse,
你知道 珍藏版的
You know, that's in the collection.
这样我就知道
That I can know I'm just gonna
放哪儿好了
put in the minutes with.
云九牌墨西哥辣酱...
Senior cloud salsa...
额 我去去就来
Um, I'll be right back.
不好意思
Uh, excuse me.
我对这些鬃毛牙刷有点疑问
I have some questions about bristle density.
是的 这些特别适合节日的时候食用
Yes, es bueno por cinco de mayo,
孩子们啊 图书馆啊
Y quinceañeras, la biblioteca.
你好
Hola.
嘿 你到底在干吗?
Hey, what do you think you're doing?
我在卖这些酱料来帮助我的奶奶
I--I am selling salsa to support mi abuela.
我的驴刚跑了
My burro has run away.
好吧 不管你是在干嘛 马特奥 我...
Right, uh, whatever this is, Mateo, I--
我不是马特奥 我是索伊·何塞
No Mateo. Soy Jose!
何塞出生在瓦哈卡边上的一个小村庄
Jose was born in a small village near oaxaca.
好 我明白了
Okay, I get it.
我明白了 我明白这样销售
I get it, I get that it's fun
很让人信服 很有趣
to play make believe,
但这很冒犯人
But this is offensive.
我很抱歉 我会停的
Like, I am sorry. I will "Estop."
是的 请停下来
Yes, please stop.
我也想啊
I am trying to.
我不开玩笑
I'm not kidding.
我也不开 尤其是我开始工作
Me neither. It's like when I "Estart"
这口音一开我就停不下来了
Doing the accent I cannot "Estop."
这个纹身真有趣
That's an interesting tattoo.
那是个独角兽吗?
Is that a unicorn?
是匹马
It's a horse
头顶上插了根铁路道的钉子
With a railroad spike through his head.
哦 懂了
I see that now.
也不是那么神奇 但是
It's not quite as magical, but...
我觉得够干净了 是啊
I think it's clean. Right.
你能不能赶紧给我打了这针?
Will you just give me the shot already?
好 好的 没问题
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.
用这根针打
The shot which comes out of this needle.
好了 让我想想
Okay, uh, huh.
这样
Okay.
我想这样有点用
I think this does something.
我用不用缠根橡胶带?
Should I have a belt?
不就打个针吗 多大点事 快点!
It's a tiny little needle, all right? Just do it!
好吧 你懂得 我只是需要 深呼吸 调整一下
All right, uh, just, uh, you know, breathe.
或者数到十准备一下什么的
Or count to ten or something like that.
准备好 我要开始了
And, uh, and away we go.
非...非常抱歉 先生!
I'm--I'm really sorry.
多喝热水
Drink a lot of water.
早告诉你了 每当我们想帮助别人的时候
Told you. That's what happens
就会搞成这样子
when you try to help people out.
什么意思 你在干什么？
What is that? What are you doing?
流沙啊
That's quicksand.
我在跟一个教手语的女孩约会
I'm dating this girl. She teaches sign language.
这是流沙 然后这是陷进去的你
This is quicksand, and this is you drowning in it.
我只是想帮帮别人
"Oh, I'm trying to help.
我为穷人们建房子
I'm building houses for poor people!"
打扰一下
Excuse me.
你知道这队要排多久嘛?
Do you know how much longer this is going to take?
我感觉自己要站不住了
I don't know how long I can keep standing.
EVERYONE
大家字幕组
你知道么 女士
You know what, young lady?
我想到一个点子能帮助你
I'm sure there's a way that we can help you out.
这边来
Right this way.
大家字幕组
谢谢你 你真绅士
Thank you! Such a gentleman.
嘿 为什么她可以插队?
Hey, why does she get to cut?
因为我们白人懂得互相帮助
Because white people help their own.
感觉我忘了我之前是怎么说话的了
It's like I forgot how to "Espeak."
太魔性了 我停不下来地想去扮演
I cannot stop playing the role.
你不是扮演 你这是歧视懂吗
It's not a role. It's a stereotype.
如果我拿出来亚洲小吃 然后像这样
How would you feel if I was handing out
你会怎么想
Asian food and I was all like,
嘿 我在米馅饼里长大
"Oh, eh, me grow up on a rice patty.
快尝尝 这是你能吃到做好吃的照烧鸡肉
"Eh, please, it most honorable teriyaki chicken.
来 再加点洋葱
Uh, so, ching-chong."
那我想你就要有麻烦了...
that would be messed up.
拉奇莎 这些表格做的不错
Nice work on those spreadsheets, Laquisha.
人们常常谈到种族歧视
Racism, you hear a lot about it,
不过 那到底是什么呢?
But what is it, really?
在接下来的一个小时里
Over the next 60 minutes...
我们将回顾一遍历史 重新审视种族
We are gonna take a journey through time and race.
真是托你们的福了 伙计们
Thanks a lot, guys.
从早晨起床
When I woke up this morning,
我就盼着能有个白人女士跟我讲种族歧视呢
I was hoping to learn about racism from a white lady.
有人能帮我选一下我的牙刷吗?
I need help with my toothbrush selection.
牙刷呀 好棘手
Toothbrushes.
你是工作人员吗?
You work here?
请大家猜猜
Here's a riddle for you
马丁·路德·金 马尔科姆·艾克斯 曼德拉
What do Martin Luther King, Malcolm X,
他们之间的共同点是什么？
And nelson Mandela all have in common?
他们都是非洲裔美国人
They were all prominent african-american leaders.
开玩笑是可以原谅的 但是你绝对不能...
It's okay to goof around, but you should never--
你从什么时候开始有种族歧视的？
So how long you been a racist?
就是今天的事 你呢?
Just today. You?
我也是
Me too.
我最近过得可真是不顺
So far it's not really working out for me.
因为当我们再回过头去看曾经种族的旧框框
Because when we look
我们就会学会去感激
past stereotypes, we learn to appreciate
自己身边各个肤色的人们
all the colors of the cloud.
听起来真美好
That sounds heavenly.
小云云 你今天教会我们好多东西
Oh, mc cool cloud, you are too much.
太多了....
Too much.
如果说我们能从今天的教训中学到什么 那就是
I think if there is any takeaway from today is this
任何一个人都可能会种族歧视 任何一个
anyone can be a racist. Anyone.
好的 明白
Okay, yes,
我的确不该给人留下那样的印象
I should not have done that impression,
但我只想澄清一下 我不是种族歧视者
But I want to be clear that I was not being racist.
我只是在批评他歧视的行为
I was making a comment about racism.
好吧 个人而言
Well, yes, personally
我真的对批评种族歧视者一点都不感冒
I'm not a fan of racist comments, so--
不 我不是那个意思
No, it's not what--
我当时夸张一下只是为了让你明白
I was exaggerating on purpose to make a point.
她只是模仿了一下
Parody.
她是在开一个这方面的玩笑
She was making a joke about racism.
没错
Yes!
哇 可以随便开种族玩笑了吗？
Well, are racist jokes okay again?
什么？
What?
嗯... 你听过那个
Okay, uh, did you hear the one
- 犹太鸟的故事吗? - 我不是这个意思 算了
- About the jewish bird? - You know what? Never mind.
啊哈 我看到一个有意思的事
Ooh, fun fact.
那个视频里给小云云配音的哥们
The dude that voiced mc cool cloud
在1994年自杀了
committed suicide in 1994.
- 太糟糕了 - 讲得通
- That's terrible. - That makes sense.
大家也要记住的一点是
We also need to remember
只是出于别人是白人就去帮助他
that helping people just because they're white
等同于因为别人不是白人
is almost as bad as discriminating
而瞧不起他
against them if they're not white.
没错它们都糟透了
It's exactly as bad.
不过他仍是在帮助别人
Well, he was still helping.
我帮那个女士是因为她年纪太大了
I was helping that lady because she was old,
而不是因为她是白人好吗？
not because she was white.
年龄歧视跟种族歧视没差别 它也是歧视
Ageism is just as racist as racism.
- 不是这样的 - 就是这样的 乔纳
- That seems untrue. - It is very true, Jonah.
现在 我建议大家
Okay, well, I think we can all
都回去工作吧
go back to work, um, unless anyone
除非有人还想提交一项种族偏见的控诉的话
Wants to file an official complaint of racial bias?
桑德拉
Sandra?
我每次去储藏室的时候
I often feel uncomfortable in the stock room.
萨尔这个猥琐的家伙
there's a man there, Sal,
都会不停地说我胸大
who makes comments about my breasts.
你说的是
Yeah, okay, what you're talking about
性骚扰
is sexual harassment,
和这个完全是两码事
And that's a whole other video.
好吧
Okay.
只是他竟然有时候还给我打电话
It's just that sometimes he calls me at home.
我们不想再看一部录像带了 桑德拉
Yeah, we're not gonna watch another video, Sandra.
好吧 真是抱歉
Okay, sorry.
现在 大家可以回去了
Okay, let's get back out there,
最后 让我们再回想一下今天学到的
And, uh, let's remember,
不因肤色区别待人
"Color blind is"...
是一种美德
"Color kind."
太棒了
Thank you.
艾米 你可以留一下吗?
Amy, could you stick around for a second?
免费尝一下我们的沙拉吗 先生?
Try a free sample of our new salsa, sir?
- 真的很好吃的 - 你这样不行 绝对不行
- It's good. - Nope, absolutely not.
人们不会从你这买沙拉的
People are not gonna buy salsa from you
除非他们觉得这是地道的沙拉
unless they think it's authentic.
你得表现得像个当地人好吗
You got to add some "Indigenous-ness."
懂吗?
You know?
表现得像个哥伦比亚人
Just put a little Vergara on it.
想买沙拉吗?
you want to buy some salsa?
为慈善的哟
Is for charity!
杰 谢谢送我项链
Oh, Jay, thank you for my necklace!
天呐 快停下来
No, stop it.
我才不会用这种腔调说话
I'm not going to put on a fake accent
我也不想在这儿虚情假意地做慈善
and I'm not gonna make up fake charities.
我们真是在做慈善啊 不信你看看
The charity is real. Yeah, check it out.
售卖所得将全部捐赠给
All the proceeds go to the la benevolencia orphanage
墨西哥诺加利斯仁爱孤儿院
In los nogales, mexico.
每个瓶子上印的小孩儿都不一样呢
There's a different child on every jar.
我觉得集齐他们可以召唤神龙了
I think it's a collect 'em all situation.
好吧 挺好的啊
Well, fine, that's great.
这可真是个非常打动人心的理由
That's a very worthy cause,
可是我觉得 我的尊严要比
But I think my dignity is worth a little bit more
做慈善赚这几个臭钱重要得多吧
than a few bucks for charity.
啊 这些都是小红人儿的
Ah, these are all Juan s's.
我已经有这个了
I've already got that one.
噢 棒呆 小黄人儿!
Oh, score, Luisa m.!
她可是生下来就没有膝盖呢
She was born without knees,
可她依然热爱跳舞
but she loves to dance.
肯定是用上半身搞定的
Must be mostly upper body stuff.
我觉得这款牙刷能解决"牙沟"问题
I think this one is good for "Tar-tar."
"丫沟"
"Tar-tar."
不 是"牙狗"
Nope, it's "Tartar."
牙钩 吖垢 牙垢
Tartar, tartar, tartar, tartar.
虽然听起来是没什么区别
I--it's all just sounding like gibberish.
好吧 让我再试一次
But um, let me just take a run up on it.
呃 我希望我的鱼可以抹上塔塔酱
Um, I like my fish with "Tar-tar" Sauce.
还是很拗口啊
It's still weird. No.
亲爱的们 呃
Guys, um--
走过路过不要错过了啊
This is benefitting a very worthwhile cause.
如果你怜悯孤儿 也喜欢辣到嗓子冒烟的辣椒酱
If you like orphans and fire-roasted peppers,
那你不来买绝对会后悔终生啊
you truly couldn't make a better purchase.
云九出品 必属精品
senior cloud es muy deliciosa.
注射流感疫苗
爽到飞起!
多令人称奇啊 是吧?
It's amazing, isn't it?
两粒药片看起来一模一样
Two pills so similar in appearance,
可是一粒能让人起死回生 另一粒却能置人于死地
But one can save a life and one can destroy it.
你看看后边 我觉得顾客快等的不耐烦了
Look, I think the people are getting impatient.
看看我们啊? 是吧?
Oh, oh, would you look at us? Huh?
就像经常一起出去钓妹子的
Gabbing like best friends
好基友一样扯起淡来了
who hang out, socially, I think.
要不你去再打开一箱疫苗
Um, why don't you open up
我们就开始工作吧
another box of vaccines, and we'll get to work.
好的 不过其他的疫苗在哪儿呢?
Okay, where are the other boxes?
就是你早上搬过来的那些啊
Well, no, the ones you brought in this morning.
那些吗? 那些早发完了啊
Oh, those? We're done. We went through those.
好吧 好吧
okay. Yeah, okay.
呃 别慌 别慌 不能慌
Uh, don't panic, don't panic, don't panic.
- 你还好吧? - 我说了别慌!
- You okay? - Don't panic!
看我说啥了?
What'd I tell you?
不用慌啊 因为我们还剩下一支疫苗
Don't panic, because we-- we still have one vaccine left.
现在你需要走到前面去
What I need you to do is go out there
告诉大家这个好消息 完美
And tell everyone that. Yeah.
我嘴里也有这个吗?
Do I have that?
五十步笑百步啊 老兄
wall to wall, brother.
哦 不是吧
Oh, no. Yeah.
天了噜 看来是了
Oh, gosh, that's what that is.
咱俩算好的了
It happens to the best of us.
那些名人的牙垢更多呢
There's celebrities that have too much tartar.
- 好吧 - 比如莱昂纳尔·里奇
- Okay. - Lionel richie.
- 你逗我 - 是真的
- No. - Yeah.
你们那儿也吃这种东西吗?
Is it similar to what you would eat in your village?
是的 是的
Si si, si
我们都吃呢
Es muy autentica.
吃起来就像我妈妈
It is just like the salsa
以前用大石碗给我做的沙拉一样
my mother would make in a bowl made from a giant rock.
那你一定参加过很多节日庆典啊
You must have enjoyed many fiestas growing up.
你是哪儿的人?
Where are you from?
我跟我姐姐
My sister and I grew up
在格兰德河河岸上的一个小村子长大
In a small village near the banks of the rio grande.
他是何塞
Jose.
谢谢了 何塞
Gracias, jose.
他们还有两个人呢
There's two of them.
今天没拿到疫苗的人明天还可以来领喔
Anybody who doesn't get a shot today will get one tomorrow.
我明天可不能请假了啊
I can't take another day off of work.
- 好吧 女士 - 而且我也不是给我自己领的 是给我宝宝的!
- Well, ma'am - And it's not just me, it's for my baby!
- 很抱歉 - 她是我唯一的希望了
I'm sorry-- and she's all that I have left
我老公在为美国战斗的时候牺牲了!
of my husband who died in the war fighting for america!
好吧 好吧 就这样吧
Okay, no, well, all right.
- 我们决定把这一支给你 你能过来一下吗 - 慢着
- We'll give you the shot, if you just come around- - Wait,
你要把我的疫苗给她?
you're gonna give her my shot?
是这样的 先生 我们应该把疫苗
Well, sir, it should probably go to the person
先给最需要的人 不是吗?
Who needs it the most, don't you think?
啊 那我怎么办? 我可是幼师啊
Uh, what about me? I teach preschool.
我还是演员呢!
I'm an actor!
- 这是优生学理论! - 你在这儿装什么圣母呢?
- This is eugenics! - Who are you to play god?
好了 别吵吵了!
Okay, again, again, again!
为了公平起见
To put it into perspective,
今天没领到疫苗的顾客
Anybody who doesn't get a vaccine today
可以到就近的别家店去取
will just have to take a short car ride to another store,
或者明天再来
or come back tomorrow.
你简直就是法西斯再世
That's what the nazis said.
万岁!
Olah!
真高兴你们能喜欢我俩的舞蹈
Gracias, gracias, we are so happy you liked our dance,
不过大家也要记得
but it is also important to remember that
拉丁美洲人也可以做医生 律师
Latinos can be doctors, and lawyers,
还有建筑师
and architects.
开玩笑的啦 这么紧张
Never mind, I'm just playing.
你们真该看看你们脸上那副表情
You should see the look on your gringo faces.
嗨起来吧!
Arriba!
来一个!
Uno mas!
不 卡门 不是你想的那样
No, Carmen, it's not what it looks like.
为了做慈善!
It's for charity!
万岁!
Olah!
顾客们请注意 现在是下午两点
Attention, shoppers, it is 2:00.
所有值早班的员工
All associates working the morning shift,
你们可以下班啦
it is time for you to leave.
你要去哪儿?
Where you going?
我们这摊事儿还没解决呢!
We're not finished here!
还没搞定呢!
We are not finished!
如果你要走的话
If you are leaving,
我希望你明白
I hope you learned that no good deed
没有付出就没有收获 还有
goes unpunished, but, also,
不管你度过了多糟糕的一天
no matter how bad a day you had,
在你轮班结束的时候 你都可以轻松一锁
at the end of your shift you get to clock out
把烦恼关在超市门里
and leave the job at the door.
不过呢 这对你们大多数人也不一定适用
Anyway, this does not pertain to most of you,
所以呢 青豆大减价啦 只要89美分喔
So green beans are on sale for 89 cents.
唱不下去了
I can't do this.
- 今天过的真糟糕啊 是吧? - 没错
- Tough day, huh? - Yeah.
我就想在这儿坐一坐
I just needed to sit.
我能也跟你一起吗?
Mind if I join you?
来吧
Be my guest.
EVERYONE
大家字幕组
我在读一篇关于紫外线的...
I was reading this article about UV rays--
嘘
Shh--
买到啦!
Got it!
真是美好的一天啊
Great day, guys
本字幕由大家字幕组原创翻译
仅供学习使用 禁止用于任何商业盈利行为
彼以国士待我 我以国士待之
用过免费优质字幕服务 而又有能力的人
有义务将这个免费服务做下去
若有心加入我们
请联系QQ群：428872140